It's Raining Men
Hi Hi
We're your weather girls
Huh huh and have we got news for you
You better listen
Get ready all you lonely girls
And leave those umbrellas at home
Alright
Mmh rising
How low girl
What sources now
We better hurry up for the first time just about half-past ten
For the first time in history it's gonna start raining men
It's raining men
Hallelujah it's raining men
Amen I'm gonna go out to run and let myself get
Absolutely soaking wet
It's raining
Men Hallelujah
Halleluja it's raining men
Every specimen
Tall, blonde
Dark and lean
Rough and tough and strong and mean
She's a single woman too
She took off to heaven
And she did what she had to do
She bought every angel and rearranged the sky
So that each and every woman could find her perfect guy
It's raining men
Hallelujah it's raining men
Amen It's raining men
Amen
Amen Amen
I feel stormy weather moving in 'Bout to begin
About to begin
Hear the thunder
Don't you lose your head
Rip off the roof and stay in bed
Oh
She's a single woman too
She took off to heaven
And she did what she had to do
She bought every angel
She rearranged the sky
So that each and every woman could find her perfect guy
Ho oh it's raining men yeah
And just
Humidity's rising
Oh oh yes rising
Is getting low, low, low, low
Low, low, low, low, is low getting low
According to all sources
Oh to all
Yeah sources 'Cos tonight for the first time
Just about half-past ten
Ho oh ho ho
For the first time in history it's gonna start raining men
Oh It's raining men
Wooh hallelujah it's raining men
Amen It's raining men
Hallelujah it's
Raining men
Amen It's raining men
Oh it's raining
Hallelujah it's raining men
Dark and lean
It's raining men
Strong and mean
Ho oh woah woah woah
Hang woah on
Woah men woah woah woah
It's woah raining oh men
Tall, I blonde can't believe
Dark and lean
Don't run away
Rough and tough
Rough and strong tough and strong and mean and mean
No no no no no
And no
I know no
How Wooh can
I see you men
Amen Uh rearranged the sky
You don't know
Oh me men